[
  
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-07-26T12:30:05.439Z",
    "history": [
      {
        "question": "What is your age?",
        "answer": "23"
      },
      {
        "question": "What symptoms are you experiencing today?",
        "answer": "sadness"
      },
      {
        "question": "How long have you been feeling this sadness?",
        "answer": "this week "
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you have any pre-existing medical conditions?",
        "answer": "nope"
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you experiencing any other symptoms besides sadness?",
        "answer": "not feeling joy, exhastion"
      }
    ],
    "userInitialStatement": {
      "theory": "i feel lonliness"
    },
    "diagnosisHistory": [
      {
        "result": "Thank you for sharing this information. Wishing you better health!",
        "timestamp": "2025-07-26T12:30:05.439Z"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-07-26T12:33:18.728Z",
    "history": [
      {
        "question": "How old are you?What is your main symptom?",
        "answer": "like throbbing pain "
      },
      {
        "question": "How long have you had this throbbing pain?",
        "answer": "after noticing its been a  week "
      },
      {
        "question": "Where exactly is this throbbing pain located?",
        "answer": "it doesnt have a single location "
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you experiencing any other symptoms along with the throbbing pain?",
        "answer": "nope "
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you have any existing medical conditions?",
        "answer": "nope "
      }
    ],
    "userInitialStatement": {
      "theory": "i feel pain in my head"
    },
    "diagnosisHistory": [
      {
        "result": "Thank you for sharing this information. Wishing you better health!",
        "timestamp": "2025-07-26T12:33:18.728Z"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-07-27T11:21:43.346Z",
    "history": [
      {
        "question": "How long have you been experiencing this?How long have you been experiencing this?",
        "answer": "from last night"
      },
      {
        "question": "What are your main symptoms?",
        "answer": "just sneezes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you have any other symptoms like a runny nose, itchy eyes, or a sore throat?",
        "answer": "yes runny nose "
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you have any known allergies?",
        "answer": "yes genetical alllergy "
      },
      {
        "question": "Are you currently taking any medications for your allergy or other conditions?",
        "answer": "i m taking sedil "
      }
    ],
    "userInitialStatement": {
      "theory": "i am feeling flu and sneazes"
    },
    "diagnosisHistory": [
      {
        "result": "Thank you for sharing this information. Wishing you better health!",
        "timestamp": "2025-07-27T11:21:43.346Z"
      }
    ]
  }
]